

CONTACT



+49 1747827269



iomaroliverreyes@gmail.com



Erlangen, Langfeldstr 35, DE



linkedin.com/in/jdreyes24

SKILLS

Technology (OS, Cloud, Web Dev.)

Systems and Networks



Softwares and Hardwares

E-Commerce and Marketing

Programming (PHP, MySQL, Etc.)

LANGUAGES





GERMAN - - -

HOBBIES









JOMAR OLIVER REYES

Success-driven and results-focused with more than 11 years of experience in the IT industry. Efficient performance with a strong background in any kind of technical support and maintenance within systems, web applications, data center, network, hardware, software, security, users and clients' virtual assistants. Workstations, servers, web clients, databases, systems, and network administration. Encompassing in problem-solving, process improvement, software testing, vendor relationships, load balancing, and scalability. Functionality & implementing technology-based solutions for business problems, along with standards and procedures. Communicate with technical and professional people verbal and written, effective teamwork, time management, organized and willing to learn new things for my career growth.

EDUCATION

BS in Information Technology

2017-present

AMA University and Colleges

Major in Software and Web App Development, Database & Security

Computer Technology

2005-2007

Asian Institute of Computer Studies

Major in Computer Hardware, Network, Systems, & Device Interfacing

EXPERIENCE

IT - Systems Engineer

2018-2020

Velocity Solutions, Inc. (MSP) - Philippines & Hong Kong

Assisting/Resolving the clients' requests & issues on Windows/Mac/Linux desktop, laptop and servers thru remote and virtual environment. Setup, implement, manage and monitor IT Systems & Infrastructure.

IT - Support Specialist

2013-2017

Wallan Trading Co. & GAMA/KAMCJ – Saudi Arabia

Provide technical support via telephone, email, tickets and remotely T-shoot & resolve a wide range of software, hardware & network issues.

IT - System & Network Administrator

2012-2013

Torch Film Productions Studios, Inc. - Philippines

Responsible for day to day operations and administration of IT Infra. Secure the systems, applications and maintain network stability.

IT - Support Engineer

2007-2012

Imaginary Friends Studio, Inc. - Philippines

Deploying, configuring, managing and maintaining of IT Systems, Network Infrastructure and provide hands-on training for the users.